Welcome back to level two.
歡迎回來第二階段 。
Now that we've recreated our header using tables for layout,
現在我們已經用表格創建了版面標頭，
we're going to continue building out the content of our email
我們將繼續建立電子郵件的內容
using multiple tables and nested tables to create columns.
使用 多個表格 和 巢狀表格 來創建 列。
It's important to know that each section should use a new table.
重要的是要 知道， 每個部分 都應使用 新表格。
We used one table for our header.
我們 在標頭中使用了一個表格 。
Now we're going to add another table to hold the image of our luchadores,
現在我們 要添加 另一個表格 來保持我們的 luchadores圖片的設定。
and then create a third table, with two nested tables inside of it,
然後創建 第三個表格 ， 裡面 有 兩個巢狀表格 。
one each for each content area.
分別用於 每個內容區塊 。
Here, you can see that we have our wrapper table,
在這裡 ， 你 可以看到，我們 有外圈表格 、
our header content table,
內容標頭表格，
and we're adding a table right below that to contain our image.
接著我們要在下方加入表格，用來顯示圖片。
If we wanted to create space between our image and our header,
如果要在圖片和標頭間加上間隔
we would normally use margin.
我們 通常會使用 margin 。
However, we get varied results in clients when using margin,
然而 ， 當我們使用 margin時在不同的客戶端上有不一樣的顯示結果 ，
and outlook.com specifically doesn't support it.
且outlook甚至不支援margin 。
Instead of relying on margin to create space
我們不用margin來建立間隔 。
in between the two tables, we're going to use padding.
我們要在兩個表格中間使用padding。
Here, we're going to add padding to the cell that is containing our image.
現在， 我們要在包含圖片的單元格中加上padding  。
Next, we want to create a table that's going to have two columns.
接下來 ， 我們要創建 一個 有兩直列的表格 。
Up until this point, we've used a single cell to contain our content.
到這裡，我們已經用單一格去包內容
However, we can use multiple cells
然而 ，我們可以使用 多個區格 。
and rely on the default behavior for them to align side by side.
並藉由預設格是使他們能夠自動對齊。
Knowing that we want each area of content to have its own table,
因為我們想要每個文字區域都有自己的表格
we're now going to put a table inside the first cell of our new table.
我們將要把表格放進去新表格的第一個單元中
This new table is where we'll apply our styles.
這個新表格中將會使用我們設定的格式 。
For our second column, we're going to repeat this same process,
在第二直列中 ， 我們要重複一樣的步驟----
adding another table within the second cell, and using that table to style the content in the second column.
在第二的單元格中加入另一個表格，接著用該表格去設定在第二列中的文字樣式
To ensure that we have an exact amount of space in between our two columns,
為了確保在兩直列中有準確的空間
we're going to use padding on the two-column cells.
要在兩直列中間使用padding 。
On the first one, we're going to add padding right of 10 pixels,
在第一個 ， 我們要在右方加上10px的留白 ，
and on the second one, we're going to add padding left of 10 pixels.
在第二個，我們要在左方加上10px的留白
This creates a total of 20 pixels space in between the two columns.
這樣在兩列中間增加了20px的空白間格
Styling the content for column one is a review of the things that we have already done.
再複習一次我們做過的，設定直列一的文字樣式
The first and last rows each contain a cell with an image for our border.
第一和最後一行各自包含了我們版面邊框的圖片
The second row contains our date,
第二 行包含 我們的日期 ，
and the third row contains our month.
第三行 包含了我們 月份。
For the first half of content in column two,
在第二行的前半文字，
we're using the same approach that we just saw.
我們使用了和剛剛一樣的方式。
Moving further into the table, we have a row with a cell that has multiple font styles.
再來看看另一個表格，我們有個設定多種文字樣式的行區塊
再來看看另一個表格，我們有個設定多種文字樣式的行區塊。
In order to do this, we need to wrap a span around each area of text that we want to be styled differently.
為了 做到這一點 ， 在要使用不一樣的樣式時，我們需要 替換 一個 span。
Here, you can see that we're using two spans to apply different font families and different font sizes.
在這裡 ， 我們分成兩個span去設定兩個不一樣的字體和文字大小
All of our hard work has paid off.
你所有的努力得到了回報。
Here, you can see that our layout looks great in Outlook
在這裡 ，不管是在IE或是Word排版引擎的outlook中， 我們的版面都看起來不錯
Now it's your turn to go back into the challenges
現在 輪到你 再進去 挑戰。
and create multiple columns using tables.
並使用 表格創建 多個列 。
And le-- Ugh.
笑。
Heh.
嘿嘿 。
Oh, I was so close.
呵呵，我 都快要完成了 。
With that "Uh-tribute." now our table is centered.
與UH-致敬。現在，你的表格。。。。
Ah, da--
啊 ， da-